This is where she crossdresses
이곳이 그녀가 남장을 하는 곳이다
one
하나
her hiding place
그녀의 은신처
Far more than this one
이것보다 훨씬 더
you know others
당신은 다른 사람을 알고
know something
뭔가를 알고
Have you been there?
거기 가봤 니?
No
아니요
With Boss Zhang’s paranoia
장보스의 편집증으로
It's hard to trust you completely
당신을 완전히 믿기는 어렵습니다
She is in Jinhai
그녀는 진하이에 있다
There aren't many people who can use it.
사용할 수 있는 사람은 많지 않습니다.
I'll make her trust me
나는 그녀가 나를 믿게 만들 것이다
The NSA has found the crow.
NSA가 까마귀를 발견했습니다.
Ran Fei was arrested
란 페이가 체포됐다
I can’t go back to the izakaya anymore
이제 다시는 이자카야에 갈 수 없어
Two actions in a row
연속된 두 가지 작업
The National Security Bureau followed closely
국가안보국도 긴밀히 뒤따랐다
i think things
내 생각엔
It's not that simple, right?
그렇게 간단하지는 않죠?
Do you doubt Gao Tianyang?
Gao Tianyang을 의심하십니까?
I can't quite believe him yet
난 아직 그 사람을 믿을 수가 없어요
I assigned the task to Ran Fei
Ran Fei에게 작업을 할당했습니다.
Logically speaking
논리적으로 말하자면
no one will notice
아무도 눈치채지 못할 거야
Gao Tianyang doesn't know either
Gao Tianyang도 모른다
his existence
그의 존재
What do you think about Zheyue?
Zheyue에 대해 어떻게 생각하세요?
something went wrong
뭔가 잘못됐어
possible
가능한
I will notify Zhou Zheyi
Zhou Zheyi에게 알립니다.
Pay attention to the people around you
주변 사람들에게 주의를 기울이세요.
You need to find a safe place as soon as possible
하루라도 빨리 안전한 곳을 찾아야 해요
Protect the trump card in your hand
손에 있는 트럼프 카드를 지켜라
I know
알아요
It's almost twenty-four hours
거의 24시간이네
He didn't say a word
그 사람은 아무 말도 하지 않았어
He's not going to speak anymore
그 사람은 더 이상 말을 하지 않을 거예요
I checked his background.
나는 그의 배경을 확인했다.
His origin was not found
그의 출신은 발견되지 않았다
The document is forged
문서가 위조되었습니다
Very likely
가능성이 매우 높다
He didn't grow up in China
그는 중국에서 자라지 않았다
His origin may be
그의 출신은 아마도
Only Boss Zhang knows
장보스만이 아는
Qin Chu
진추
Shiqi has left
시치가 떠났다
Life is in danger
생명이 위험하다
Walk
걷다
It’s almost the same as Gao Tianyang’s judgment.
Gao Tianyang의 판단과 거의 동일합니다.
On Zhou Shiqi’s computer keyboard
Zhou Shiqi의 컴퓨터 키보드에서
Sprayed with poison
독을 뿌렸다
causing her to be poisoned
그녀를 중독시키게 만들어
Over there at the Toxicology Division
저기 독성학 부서에 있어요
There are also results
결과도 있어요
It's the same poison as Shi Lei's
시레이와 같은 독이네
What situation did Zhou Shiqi explain?
Zhou Shiqi는 어떤 상황을 설명했습니까?
Two copies she kept
그녀가 보관한 사본 두 권
About Zheyue
Zheyue 소개
Video delivering customer data
고객 데이터를 전달하는 동영상
Everything was ruined by Ran Fei
란페이 때문에 모든 게 망가졌어
Network information security
네트워크 정보 보안
is part of national security
국가 안보의 일부이다
If Zhou Shiqi
저우시치라면
What is said is true
말한 내용은 사실입니다
Zheyue's behavior
Zheyue의 행동
Already suspected of violating the law
이미 법 위반 혐의를 받고 있음
But we are now
하지만 우리는 지금
Only Zhou Shiqi’s confession
오직 저우시치의 고백
no other evidence yet
다른 증거는 아직 없어
There is no way to deal with Zhou Zheyi
Zhou Zheyi를 상대할 방법이 없습니다.
Conduct in-depth investigation
심층 조사 실시
I will report the situation to my superiors
나는 상사에게 상황을 보고할 것이다
Contact relevant departments
관련 부서에 문의하세요
Data center for Zheyue
Zheyue 데이터 센터
Do a safety check
안전 점검을 해보세요
As for Zhou Zheyi
저우저이(Zhou Zheyi)의 경우
Tianyang has his plan
Tianyang에는 그의 계획이 있습니다
clear
분명한
Don't worry, you two.
걱정하지 마세요, 두 분.
We all operate legally
우리는 모두 합법적으로 사업을 운영합니다.
Won't mess around
장난하지 않을거야
For safety reasons
안전상의 이유로
Cut off Zheyue
Zheyue를 차단하세요
and game data transfer
게임 데이터 전송
within a short period of time
짧은 시간 안에
I can't give it to you any more
더 이상 너에게 줄 수 없어
Data provided
제공된 데이터
Zheyue
절웨
is a secret agent game in china
중국의 비밀 요원 게임입니다
largest database
가장 큰 데이터베이스
We must focus on protecting it
우리는 그것을 보호하는 데 집중해야 합니다
This time Guoan
이번에는 궈안
Suddenly come to stir up trouble
갑자기 와서 문제를 일으키다
Let Boss Zhang’s identity be exposed
장보스의 신원을 공개하자
We really lost a lot
우리는 정말 많은 것을 잃었습니다
yes
예
Guoan this time
이번에는 구오안
To find the crow so quickly
까마귀를 그렇게 빨리 찾으려면
I really didn't expect that
정말 그럴 줄은 예상 못했어요
correct
옳은
this mission
이 임무
Who else knows
또 누가 알겠어
Except Boss Zhang
장보스 빼고
Only Yao Yao
야오야오만이
Boss Zhang must have no problem
장보스는 문제가 없을 것 같아요
Yao Yao
야오야오
Don't worry, I'll find out.
걱정하지 마세요. 제가 알아볼게요.
It seems that Guoan
궈안인 것 같아요
Already targeting you
이미 당신을 타겟팅하고 있습니다.
Take care of yourself
몸 조심하세요
I will be careful
조심하겠습니다
what are you doing here
여기서 뭐해?
I need to find a safe place
안전한 곳을 찾아야 해요
For example, your home
예를 들어, 당신의 집
impossible
불가능한
Let’s go in first
먼저 들어가자
Not very safe here
여기는 그다지 안전하지 않아요
How is your investigation going?
조사는 어떻게 진행되고 있나요?
Technology section takes your photo
기술 섹션에서 사진을 찍습니다.
and get before
그리고 그 전에 도착
After you disguised yourself
변장한 뒤
Photos of missions
임무 사진
compared
비교하다
Confirm it is a person
사람인지 확인
Probably now
아마도 지금은
in each system
각 시스템에서
Entered your information
귀하의 정보를 입력했습니다
Ready to launch investigation
조사 개시 준비 완료
I believe
나는 믿는다
You can definitely place me well
넌 분명 나를 잘 자리잡을 수 있을 거야
After all, you don’t want it either
결국 너도 원하지 않잖아
I fell into the hands of the national security
나는 국가 안보의 손에 넘어갔다
I don’t believe that in Jinhai
진하이에서는 그런 말을 믿지 않아요
You don't have it
당신은 그것을 가지고 있지 않습니다
Any other contacts?
다른 연락처는 없나요?
Yes, I have
네, 있어요
But not as good as you
하지만 너만큼 좋지는 않아
Are you forcing me?
나한테 강요하는 거야?
I can't help it either
나도 어쩔 수가 없어
How long do you plan to stay here
여기에 얼마나 오래 머물 계획인가요?
When it’s time to leave, I’ll leave naturally
떠날 시간이 되면 자연스럽게 떠날게
Do you trust me that much?
나를 그렇게 믿나요?
The organization doesn’t trust you yet
조직은 아직 당신을 신뢰하지 않습니다
But I'm different from them
하지만 나는 그들과 달라
I believe
나는 믿는다
You will definitely protect me
넌 반드시 나를 지켜줄 거야
Right
오른쪽
But now we both
하지만 이제 우리 둘 다
There's big trouble
큰 문제가 생겼어요
What
무엇
Ran Fei knows my identity
란페이는 내 정체를 알고 있다
The National Security Bureau is targeting him
국가안전보위부가 그를 표적으로 삼고 있다
conduct interrogation
심문을 하다
Didn't hold me accountable
나에게 책임을 묻지 않았어
Once he collapses
일단 그가 쓰러지면
tell me who i am
내가 누구인지 말해줘
We're both screwed
우리 둘 다 망했어
What should I do?
어떻게 해야 하나요?
Otherwise, you can think of a way
그렇지 않으면 방법을 생각할 수 있습니다.
Make him unable to speak
그 사람이 말을 못하게 만들어
let me get rid of him
내가 그 사람을 없애게 해줘
It's not like you haven't done it before
이전에 해본 적이 없는 것과는 다릅니다
He is different from Xiao Yi
샤오이랑은 달라
It's impossible to succeed
성공하는 것은 불가능하다
You don't need to remind me repeatedly
나에게 반복해서 상기시킬 필요는 없습니다.
I have the handle in your hands
손잡이는 네 손에 있어
You don't have to be so nervous
너무 긴장할 필요는 없어
I was just kidding
농담이에요
i know this is a
나도 알아 이게
Mission impossible
불가능한 임무
I have no thoughts now
지금은 아무 생각이 없어
joking with you
너랑 농담하는 거야
Do not worry
걱정 하지마
He won't betray you
그 사람은 당신을 배신하지 않을 거예요
are you sure
확실합니까
betray you
당신을 배신하다
It's like betraying me
나를 배신하는 것과 같으니
Why do you trust him so much?
왜 그 사람을 그토록 신뢰합니까?
certainly
틀림없이
I have confidence
나는 자신감을 갖고 있다
You can rest assured
안심하셔도 됩니다
Did you have meal
식사하셨나요?
I have not eaten
나 안 먹었어
Nothing at all
전혀 아무것도
Only instant noodles
인스턴트 라면만
Very good
매우 좋은
So fragrant
너무 향기로워
You don't want to try it
당신은 그것을 시도하고 싶지 않아
you eat
먹어
I know you are good at cooking
나는 당신이 요리를 잘한다는 것을 안다.
There's something you need to tell me
나한테 꼭 말해줘야 할 게 있어
What's up
무슨 일이야
How did you find Shiqi?
Shiqi를 어떻게 찾았나요?
I don’t know the specifics either.
저도 구체적인 내용은 모릅니다.
No, Section Chief Gao
아니, 가오 과장
I checked it in the agent game.
에이전트게임에서 확인해봤습니다.
I'm not responsible for that part
그 부분은 제가 책임지지 않습니다
That female colleague of yours
당신의 그 여자 동료
yes
예
I told you a long time ago
내가 오래전에 말했지
You want to avoid these situations
이런 상황을 피하고 싶으신가요?
It's best to tell me in advance
미리 말씀해 주시는 게 좋을 것 같아요
what action do you take
당신은 어떤 조치를 취합니까?
There's nothing I can do now
이제 내가 할 수 있는 일은 아무것도 없어
I am one
나는 하나이다
People who hide in Tibet
티베트에 숨어있는 사람들
What about Jinhai’s job?
진하이의 직업은 어떻습니까?
I don’t have to be responsible anymore
더 이상 책임질 필요 없어
Even if I want to tell you
말하고 싶어도
There's nothing I can do
내가 할 수 있는 일은 아무것도 없어
Then don't blame me
그럼 나를 비난하지 마세요
I realized it later
나중에 깨달았어요
This excuse works well.
이 변명은 잘 먹힌다.
I can't control others
나는 다른 사람을 통제할 수 없다
If you have other tasks
다른 업무가 있으면
I hope you won't do it for now
지금은 그러지 않기를 바라요
After all, I want to live longer
결국 나는 오래 살고 싶다.
that woman
그 여자
can you handle it
감당할 수 있어?
First time going to an izakaya
이자카야에 처음 가보는데
she is with you
그녀는 당신과 함께 있어요
that time
그때
You noticed me
당신은 나를 알아 차렸다
to be precise
정확하게 말하자면
I noticed you two
난 너희 둘을 알아차렸어
She should be interested in you
그 사람이 너한테 관심이 있을 텐데
What's the meaning
무슨 뜻인가요?
meaning between men and women
남자와 여자 사이의 의미
But this is fine
하지만 이건 괜찮아요
The more she likes you
그 사람이 당신을 좋아할수록
the safer i am
난 더 안전해
Why
왜
people who like themselves
자신을 좋아하는 사람들
is the best to control
통제하는 것이 최선이다
Like Xiao Yi
샤오이처럼
What do you want
당신은 무엇을 원하나요
How long will you stay here with me?
언제까지 여기 나와 함께 있을 거예요?
Didn't I say that?
내가 그렇게 말하지 않았나요?
When it's time to go
갈 시간이 되면
I will leave of course
나는 당연히 떠날 것이다
But now I
하지만 지금 나는
Quite like it here
여기 꽤 좋아
Your situation is very dangerous now
지금 당신의 상황은 매우 위험합니다
There's nothing you can do if you stay.
가만히 있으면 할 수 있는 게 아무것도 없어요.
Section Chief Gao wants to ask me
가오 과장이 나한테 묻고 싶어
Next
다음
What more tasks do you need to complete?
완료하려면 어떤 작업이 더 필요합니까?
Talking around in circles about me
맴돌면서 나에 대해 얘기하고 있어
Yewu already knows that you were exposed
예우는 당신이 노출된 것을 이미 알고 있습니다.
Still leaving you in Jinhai
아직도 당신을 진하이에 남겨두고 있어요
perform tasks
업무를 수행하다
You said they wanted to achieve their goals
당신은 그들이 목표를 달성하고 싶다고 말했어요
I don't care about other people's lives either
나도 남의 인생엔 관심없어
This is what our industry is like
우리 업계가 이렇다
when you are useful
당신이 유용할 때
Whatever happens
어떤 일이
It's no use turning against others.
남에게 등을 돌리는 것은 아무 소용이 없습니다.
Isn’t that what Guoan is like?
구오안은 그렇지 않나요?
if they knew
그들이 알았다면
you have contact with us
당신은 우리와 연락이
what will happen
무슨 일이 일어날 것
Guoan knows you are here with me
Guoan은 당신이 나와 함께 여기 있다는 것을 알고 있습니다
We're both screwed
우리 둘 다 망했어
look
바라보다
It's the same in every line
모든 라인에서 동일합니다
Maybe one day
어쩌면 언젠가
career is over
경력은 끝났어
It’s better to enjoy yourself in time
시간 맞춰서 즐겨보는 게 좋을 것 같아요
You can stay here with me
당신은 나와 함께 여기에 머물 수 있습니다
But don't cause trouble
하지만 문제를 일으키지는 마세요
Don't go out easily
쉽게 나가지 마세요
This is my bottom line
이것이 내 결론이다
Finished explaining it
설명을 마치겠습니다
I'm full too
나도 배불러
Very tired today
오늘은 매우 피곤하다
This is the bedroom, right?
여기가 침실이죠?
double bed
더블 베드
It really feels like home
정말 집 같은 느낌이에요
The last one was with you
마지막은 너와 함께였어
People with such an atmosphere
이런 분위기를 가진 사람들
already dead
이미 죽었어
Then you better pray
그럼 기도하는 게 좋을 거야
You are luckier than him
당신은 그 사람보다 운이 좋다
Has anyone been looking for crows lately?
최근에 까마귀를 찾는 사람이 있나요?
Quite a few
꽤 많은 수
give me a piece of information
나에게 정보 하나를 줘
Send it to you immediately
즉시 보내주세요.
Good morning
좋은 아침이에요
How was your rest?
휴식은 어땠나요?
I didn’t know you had breakfast
나는 당신이 아침을 먹었는지 몰랐어요
What flavor do you like to eat?
어떤 맛을 먹고 싶나요?
Chinese style Western style
중국식 서양식
I did it all
내가 다 했어
I don't have the habit of eating breakfast
나는 아침을 먹는 습관이 없다.
Good habits should be developed slowly
좋은 습관은 천천히 키워야 한다
Eat it yourself
직접 먹어보세요
All right
괜찮은
we investigated
우리는 조사했다
Zheyue company’s data center
Zheyue 회사의 데이터 센터
Nothing suspicious
의심스러운 것은 없습니다
When Shiqi started blackmailing
Shiqi가 협박을 시작했을 때
Maybe Zhou Zheyi
아마 저우저이(Zhou Zheyi)
Already thought of countermeasures
대책은 이미 생각 중
But we are now
하지만 우리는 지금
There is no evidence to prove
증명할 증거가 없습니다
Zheyue is a secret agent mission
Zheyue는 비밀 요원 임무입니다
The data source behind
뒤에 있는 데이터 소스
So it's hard for us now
그래서 지금 우리는 힘들다
Catch Zhou Zheyi
Zhou Zheyi를 잡아라
Direct evidence of espionage
간첩의 직접적인 증거
He is a tough opponent
그 사람은 힘든 상대야.
Philosophy means having
철학은 가지고 있다는 뜻이다.
Influential companies
영향력 있는 기업
This matter needs to be considered in the long run
이 문제는 장기적으로 고려해야 한다
Boss Zhang is staying at your house
장보스가 당신 집에 머물고 있어요
Be careful
조심하세요
She still needs me now
그녀는 지금도 내가 필요해
She won't do anything to me
그 사람은 나한테 아무 짓도 안 할 거야
I won't attack you
나는 당신을 공격하지 않습니다
Why are we staying at your house?
우리는 왜 당신 집에 머물고 있습니까?
Sheep entering tiger's mouth
호랑이 입으로 들어가는 양
Keep yourself clean
자신을 깨끗하게 유지하세요
Have your breakfast
아침식사하세요
Yes
예
I know recently
최근에 알아요
Indeed it is online
실제로는 온라인이다
There are some rumors
소문이 좀 있는데
But since it’s a rumor
하지만 소문이니까
That must not be true
그건 사실이 아니어야 해요
But anyway
하지만 어쨌든
It must be us
분명 우리일 거야
There are things I didn’t do well
내가 잘 못한 것도 있고
Management must be strengthened in the future
앞으로 관리 강화해야
OK
좋아요
Please rest assured, leaders
안심하세요 리더님들
goodbye
안녕히 가세요
Find me, Mr. Zhou
저를 찾아주세요, 저우 선생님
Something happened to Shiqi
Shiqi에게 무슨 일이 일어났나요?
problem occurs
문제가 발생하다
What happened to her
그녀에게 무슨 일이 일어 났니
National Security Bureau
국가안보국
Involved in investigation
조사에 참여
How did they get involved?
그들은 어떻게 참여하게 되었나요?
Yeah, I want to know too
응, 나도 알고 싶어
What's the problem?
뭐가 문제 야?
I asked you to investigate Shiqi's matter
나는 당신에게 Shiqi의 문제를 조사해달라고 요청했습니다.
Have you mentioned it to anyone?
누구한테도 언급한 적 있나요?
my ex-boyfriend
내 전 남자친구
He seems to know too
그 사람도 아는 것 같더라
how so
어떻게 그렇게
I went to meet Shi Qi that day
나는 그날 Shi Qi를 만나러 갔다
He wants to find me
그 사람이 나를 찾고 싶어해요
Suddenly he hit me
갑자기 그 사람이 나를 때렸어요
I do not know what to do
나는 무엇을 해야할지 모르겠다
I can only tell him
그 사람에게만 말할 수 있어요
This is a work assignment
이건 업무 할당이야
But don’t worry, Mr. Zhou
하지만 걱정하지 마세요, 저우 선생님
I just told him it was work.
나는 방금 그에게 일이라고 말했습니다.
Other redundant
기타 중복
I didn't tell him anything
나는 그에게 아무 말도 하지 않았다.
Then this has to do with the National Security Bureau
그럼 이건 국가안전보위부와 관련이 있는 거죠
What does it matter?
그것은 무슨 상관이야?
he has a brother
그에게는 형제가 있어요
It's from the National Security Bureau
국가안전보위부에서 온 내용이에요
Will it
그럴까요?
What did he say
그는 무엇을 말 했는가
Sorry Mr. Zhou
미안해요 저우 선생님
Did I do this?
내가 이런 짓을 한 걸까?
screwed up
망했다
it's okay no problem
괜찮아 문제 없어
fine
괜찮은
That's nothing
그건 별거 아니야
I'll go out
나는 나갈 것이다
I checked
나는 확인했다
no problem
괜찮아요
They can't find anything
그들은 아무것도 찾을 수 없습니다
Hello
안녕하세요
let's meet
만나자
Thanks
감사해요
Have you checked Shi Qi?
Shi Qi를 확인해 보셨나요?
Why are you checking her?
왜 그녀를 확인하고 있습니까?
I want to know Zhou Zheyi
나는 Zhou Zheyi를 알고 싶다
Why do you want to check her?
왜 그녀를 확인하고 싶습니까?
you don't tell me
당신은 나에게 말하지 않습니다
I can only check it myself
나 혼자만 확인할 수 있어
What did you find out?
무엇을 알아냈나요?
Someone broke the news in the spy game
누군가 스파이 게임에서 소식을 전했습니다.
Said Zheyue leaked user information
Zheyue가 사용자 정보를 유출했다고 말했습니다
The whistleblower is Shiqi
내부 고발자는 Shiqi입니다.
So Zhou Zheyi
소 저우 저이(So Zhou Zheyi)
That’s why I asked you to check her out
그래서 내가 그 사람한테 확인해 보라고 한 거야
You can also enter the game
게임에 입장할 수도 있습니다.
It's also possible
그것은 또한 가능하다
The people in Yewu told him
예우 사람들이 그에게 말했다.
So he knows my identity
그래서 그 사람이 내 정체를 알아요
That's why I was asked to investigate
그래서 조사를 해보라고 하더군요
It's very possible
매우 가능합니다
Are you still in contact with Guoan?
아직도 구오안과 연락하고 지내나요?
I still have contact with Gao Tianyang
나는 아직도 Gao Tianyang과 연락을 취하고 있습니다.
Are you helping him?
당신은 그를 돕고 있나요?
He doesn't need me
그 사람은 내가 필요하지 않아
After you left that day
그날 네가 떠난 뒤
I've been thinking
생각을 해봤는데
I really can't
난 정말 못해요
If this continues
이것이 계속된다면
Shi Qi threatens them
Shi Qi가 그들을 위협합니다.
They are going to get rid of her
그들은 그녀를 제거할 예정이다
I really don't dare to think about it
정말 감히 생각해 볼 수가 없어요
Will one day
언젠가는
I ended up like this too
나도 결국 이렇게 됐다
do you know
당신은 알고 있나요
Can you come to me today
오늘 나한테 와줄 수 있어?
I'm very happy
나는 매우 행복 해요
I have been worried about you before
나는 예전부터 당신을 걱정한 적이 있었습니다.
I'm worried that you will continue to help Yewu
계속해서 예우를 도와줄까 걱정돼요
Will sink deeper and deeper
점점 더 깊게 가라앉을 거야
Then will you help me?
그러면 나를 도와주실 건가요?
help
돕다
What can I do for you?
내가 당신을 위해 무엇을 할 수?
I want to find out Zhou Zheyi
Zhou Zheyi를 알아보고 싶습니다.
true identity
진정한 정체성
This thing for me
나를 위한 이 것
is an opportunity
기회이다
Why are you checking Zhou Zheyi?
Zhou Zheyi를 확인하는 이유는 무엇입니까?
Leave it to the National Security Bureau
국가안전보위부에 맡겨라
This is my last chance
이번이 마지막 기회야
you
너
will you help me
당신은 날 도움이 될 것입니다
help
돕다
Try my best
최선을 다할
Thanks
감사해요
what do we do
우리는 무엇을해야합니까
I heard him in the office during the day
낮에 사무실에서 그 사람 얘기 들었어
Video with others
다른 사람들과 함께하는 영상
say what
뭐라고
Someone has come to check
누군가 확인하러 왔습니다
Can't find anything
아무것도 찾을 수 없습니다
Is he using a mobile phone or a computer?
그 사람은 휴대폰을 사용하고 있나요, 아니면 컴퓨터를 사용하고 있나요?
computer
컴퓨터
Then go to his office and check it out.
그럼 그의 사무실로 가서 확인해 보세요.
Isn’t it over?
끝나지 않았나요?
most of his time
대부분의 시간
They all stay in the office
다들 사무실에 있어
It's hard for me to get a chance
기회를 잡기가 어렵네요
And I don't know either
그리고 나도 모르겠어
How to get into his computer
그의 컴퓨터에 들어가는 방법
I have a way
나에겐 방법이 있다
Why are the lights dark?
조명은 왜 어두워요?
Not open for business
영업하지 않음
Why is it closed?
왜 닫혀 있나요?
Not even a notification
알림도 안오고
Something happens temporarily
일시적으로 문제가 발생함
The landlady looks like
집주인이 닮음
Still quite reliable
그래도 꽤 믿음직함
I just recharged money
방금 돈을 충전했어요
Isn't she running away?
그 사람 도망치는 거 아니야?
Lao Huang
라오 황
Don't worry
괜찮아요
project
프로젝트
It's over for now
지금은 끝났어
I originally wanted to have two more drinks with you
원래는 너랑 두 잔 더 마시고 싶었는데
You said you're used to this place's food?
이 집 음식에 익숙하다고 했죠?
Not coming for a few days
며칠 동안 안 오네요
I quite like this.
나는 이것을 아주 좋아합니다.
Okay, come with me
알았어, 나랑 같이 가자
Change one
하나 바꾸세요
That one is good too
저것도 좋은데
Which one?
어느 것?
Front
앞쪽
Morning aunt
아침 이모
morning
아침
Here it is
여기있어
Zhou Zheyi's office
저우저이의 사무실
The code lock is here
코드락은 여기 있어요
I'll tell you the password later
비밀번호는 나중에 알려드릴게요
receive
받다
I thought you only made Japanese food
일본음식만 만드는줄 알았는데
Then you underestimate me too much
그럼 넌 나를 너무 과소평가하는구나
It seems that I know you well
나는 당신을 잘 아는 것 같습니다
Not enough
부족한
It doesn't matter
그것은 중요하지 않습니다
There will be plenty of time in the future
앞으로도 시간은 많을 것이다
Let you slowly understand
천천히 이해해주세요
What do you want to eat at night
밤에 뭐 먹을래?
casual
평상복
Then I'll make the arrangements myself.
그럼 제가 직접 준비하겠습니다.
Just be happy yourself
그냥 스스로 행복해지세요
Hello
안녕하세요
your takeaway
테이크아웃
Thanks
감사해요
Wait a moment
잠깐만요
Can I discuss something with you?
당신과 뭔가 논의할 수 있을까요?
What's the matter?
무슨 일이야?
I went to an izakaya that day
그날 이자카야에 갔어요
I thought something happened to you
너한테 무슨 일이 일어난 줄 알았는데
I'm fine
잘 지내요
Do not worry
걱정 하지마
But there's something
하지만 뭔가가 있어요
I still need your help
난 아직 네 도움이 필요해
The last sample was destroyed.
마지막 샘플이 파괴되었습니다.
Need to get another one
하나 더 구해야 해
impossible
불가능한
Nana, let’s eat
나나, 밥 먹자
Mr. Zhou
저우 씨
Nothing missing?
빠진 건 없나요?
Last time I saw what you liked to eat
저번에 네가 뭘 좋아하는지 봤어
I ordered a little casually
조금 여유롭게 주문했어요
Quite attentive
꽤 세심함
Want a drink?
한잔 원하시나요?
Have some
좀 드세요
Do you have something to tell me today?
오늘 나한테 할 말 있어?
Let me toast you first
내가 먼저 건배하자
Why do you respect me first?
왜 나를 먼저 존중합니까?
Shiqi’s matter is resolved
Shiqi의 문제가 해결되었습니다.
Wish you
당신을 기원합니다
overcome obstacles
장애물을 극복하다
Thanks
감사해요
so I
그래서 나는
No more beating around the bush
더 이상 덤불 주변에서 두들겨 패지 마세요.
I've always had a question to ask you
나는 항상 당신에게 물어보고 싶은 질문이 있었습니다
What is your identity?
당신의 정체성은 무엇입니까?
What do you think I am?
내가 어떤 사람이라고 생각하세요?
same as me
나와 같은
You are also from Yewu
너도 예우 출신이구나
night fog
밤안개
I don't seem to understand
이해하지 못하는 것 같아요
what are you saying
당신이 무슨 말을하는거야
Mr. Zhou
저우 씨
Even the courage to admit one's identity
자신의 정체성을 인정하는 용기조차
None?
없음?
Why do you say that?
왜 그런 말을 해?
Because you trust me too much
당신이 나를 너무 신뢰하기 때문에
My trust makes you uneasy
내 믿음이 널 불안하게 만들어
also possible
또한 가능
It's because of my own reasons
나만의 이유 때문이야
I never believed it
나는 그것을 결코 믿지 않았다
Trust without reason
이유 없이 신뢰하다
What do you think
어떻게 생각하나요
why do i trust you
내가 왜 당신을 믿나요?
because you know
당신이 알고 있기 때문에
I am also a night fog person
나도 밤안개 사람이다
That's why you asked me to investigate Shiqi
그래서 나한테 Shiqi를 조사해 달라고 한 거야
this matter
이 문제
When it was first exposed
처음 공개됐을 때
You've already thought about it
당신은 이미 그것에 대해 생각했습니다
Want to find her and get rid of her
그녀를 찾아 없애고 싶어
So you must find one
그래서 당신은 하나를 찾아야합니다
Very trustworthy people
매우 신뢰할 수 있는 사람들
Who is there?
거기 누구야?
Better than people in the organization
조직의 사람들보다 낫습니다.
More trustworthy
더욱 신뢰할 수 있는
Or rather
아니면 오히려
Use it in the sense that I am Mr. Yu
내가 유씨라는 의미로 사용하세요
Is it right
맞아
Mr. Zhou
저우 씨
I would like to know
나는 알고 싶다
why are you telling me this
왜 나한테 이런 말을 하는 거야?
I know you won't admit it
네가 인정하지 않을 거라는 걸 알아
but one thing
하지만 한 가지
I must remind you
나는 당신에게 상기시켜 주어야합니다
Someone has already started
누군가 이미 시작했습니다.
I'm doubting you
나는 당신을 의심하고 있습니다
who is it
누구야?
Huang Zicheng
황쯔쳉
your ex-boyfriend
너의 전 남자친구
right
오른쪽
He has always suspected you
그 사람은 항상 당신을 의심했어요
I suspect you are from Yewu
당신이 Yewu 출신인 것 같아요
you haven't told me yet
넌 아직 나한테 말하지 않았어
why are you telling me this
왜 나한테 이런 말을 하는 거야?
Because of today’s meal
오늘 식사 때문에
It was he who asked me to treat you to food
나에게 당신에게 음식을 대접하라고 요청한 사람은 바로 그 사람이었습니다
Let you treat me to dinner
나한테 저녁을 대접해줄게
Then find out my identity
그럼 내 정체를 알아봐
Not only that
뿐만 아니라
He should be already
그는 이미
It's in your office
네 사무실에 있어
What are you doing in my office?
내 사무실에서 뭐 하는 거야?
Of course I want to investigate you
물론 난 당신을 조사하고 싶어요
Find out you and Yewu
당신과 Yewu를 알아보세요
evidence of connection
연결의 증거
Who told him to do this?
누가 그에게 이렇게 하라고 했나요?
National Security Bureau
국가안보국
of course not
당연히 아니지
It's impossible for the National Security Bureau
국가안전보위부로서는 불가능하다
Let him do this
그 사람이 이렇게 하게 놔둬
Uncertain things
불확실한 것들
It's what he wants
그게 그 사람이 원하는 거야
find out your identity
당신의 정체를 알아내세요
Help Gao Tianyang
가오텐양을 도와주세요
Get rid of the threat of night fog
밤안개의 위협을 제거하세요
Why are you telling me this?
왜 나한테 이런 말을 하는 거야?
Because Mr. Yu
유 씨 때문에
Mr. Yu doesn't want you to get into trouble
유 씨는 당신이 문제에 빠지는 것을 원하지 않습니다
And if something happens to you
그리고 당신에게 무슨 일이 생기면
He will never let me go
그 사람은 절대 날 놓아주지 않을 거야
I can't refuse Huang Zicheng
나는 황자성을 거절할 수 없다
Make him doubt me
그 사람이 나를 의심하게 만들어요
So you come and tell me
그러니까 네가 와서 나한테 말해봐
Mr. Zhou
저우 씨
I really have
나는 정말
There is no way out
탈출구가 없어
I don’t want to be arrested by the national security
나는 국가 안보에 체포되고 싶지 않습니다
I don’t even want to stay in Jinhai
진하이에 머물고 싶지도 않아요
This place is sitting there waiting to die.
이 곳은 거기 앉아서 죽기를 기다리고 있습니다.
I want to leave here
나는 여기서 떠나고 싶다
I hope you can help me
당신이 나를 도울 수 있기를 바랍니다
May I
나는 할 수있다
I will help you
내가 당신을 도울 것입니다
You think this is
당신은 이것이라고 생각합니다
Promise me
약속해줘
Promise you
네게 약속한다
thank you for telling me all this
나에게 이 모든 것을 말해줘서 고마워요
I am very happy
나는 매우 행복하다
You and I are
당신과 나는
People in the same camp
같은 캠프에 있는 사람들
Don't run
뛰지 마세요
How dare you break into the office
감히 사무실에 침입하다니
What are you doing
뭐하세요
play a game
게임을하다
what game
무슨 게임
Agent mission
에이전트 임무
game
게임
Let's talk to the police later.
나중에 경찰한테 얘기하자.
take away
빼앗다
Take a walk
산책하다
Don't, don't, don't
하지마, 하지마, 하지마